

# Yury Kastsen

+48881096343

spkava@gmail.com

Wrocław

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen">https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen</a>

Website: <a href="https://mental.gatsbyjs.io">https://mental.gatsbyjs.io</a> **Github:** https://github.com/kastsen

#### Introduction

I help bring concepts to life, ensuring projects are launched on time. Programming, product support, and enhancement all fall within my scope of responsibilities. I hope to see the world change, so I always strive to connect my work and life with progressive projects.

My technology stack includes: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Webpack, Pixi.js, Create.js, Three.js, Gatsby.js, HTML5, Pug.js, CSS3, SCSS, Bash, Git and more.

I'm now looking forward to using my skills and experience in a fulfilling position.

### **Experience**

12/2022 - until now **Web Games Developer** 

**QS** Games

Web Games Development and maintenance service:

· CORAL ISLE 2 - https://coralisle2.guartsoft.com/index.html

· FARLAND - https://farland.quartsoft.com/index.html

· PAPAYA - https://papaya.quartsoft.com/index.html

· Skills: JavaScript · Typescript · Webpack · Pixi JS · Create JS · React · Redux ·

HTML5 · Git · mySQL · REST API

03/2020 - 08/2022 **Playable Ads Developer** 

Vizor Games

Playable ads development. Framework development and support. Build automatisation. Optimization of processes and tasks, work with the team. Skills: Node.js · npm · Webpack · JavaScript · Matter JS · Bash · Pixi.js · Spine

Animations · Tiled · HTML5 · SVN · JSON · ES6+

12/2019 - 03/2020 **Front-end Developer** 

Bamboo Apps

Project support and maintenance service. Interviews, onboarding for new employees. Skills: JavaScript · Node.js · Express.js · mySQL · CSS3 · SCSS ·

SPA · UI · Github · Webpack · Git · SASS · AJAX · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · npm · ES6+ · API · Pug.js

05/2019 - 05/2020 Front-end Development Speaker

School MyFreedomIT

Skills: Public Speaking · CSS3 · HTML5 · Git · Bootstrap · JavaScript

02/2018 - 11/2019 Front-end Developer

Logic Software Inc.

Work with a team, including a team of designers, developers and marketing. June training. Support and optimization of the project. Skills: Node.js  $\cdot$  JavaScript  $\cdot$  CSS3  $\cdot$  SCSS  $\cdot$  React  $\cdot$  Web Design  $\cdot$  Agile Methodologies  $\cdot$  Scrum  $\cdot$  UX  $\cdot$  jQuery  $\cdot$  Webpack  $\cdot$  Git  $\cdot$  SASS  $\cdot$  AJAX  $\cdot$  JSX  $\cdot$  Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)  $\cdot$  JSON  $\cdot$  npm  $\cdot$  Yarn  $\cdot$  ES6+  $\cdot$  API  $\cdot$  PHP  $\cdot$  mySQL

06/2015 - 12/2017 Web Development Specialist

inAweb

Web sites design, development and support. Building custom WordPress themes and plugins. HTML-markup, PHP, MySQL, jQuery.

05/2011 - 08/2015 **Content Manager** 

**Cultutal Daily News Portal** 

Content management, digital marketing, planning and implementation of audience engagement activities, generation of new ideas, community management.

## **Knowledge and skills**

Languages:

Russian (proficient) Byelorussian (proficient) English (intermediate) Czech (pre-intermediate) Polish (pre-intermediate)

Skills:

JavaScript	HTML5	CSS3	SASS	webpa	ick n	ode.js	npm	PixiJS	WebGL
ReactJS	ReactJS React Native		sbyJS \	Web Game	es Th	ree.js	Project planning		
Team management B		Bash	MySQL	OOP	Redux	Agil	Agile methodologies		

### **Education**

Level of education

University

2015 - 2016

Erasmus+ EVS
Politologie

2008 - 2012

BSPU
Philology. Literature. Journalism

### **Certification and courses**

2019 **School MyfreedomIT** Javascript, React JS. Front-end Development

2013 Používání vizuálních symbolů a tvůrčích přístupů

Prague

Známost s českou zkušeností v použití vizuálních symbolů a kreativních

přístupů k sociální činnosti.

### **Hobbies**

Music Nature Quad roller skating